I committed at least in my head to doing
a video every single day and today I
have no idea what the subject is I just
want to get it out there before I go to
bed I had a sore throat all day my sore
throat is a symptom that I've been over
I've been doing too much and I have to
take it more easy but it's been here for
a few days and I don't really know how
to take it more easy but I've been
taking it so I'm just gonna keep keep it
on keep working but I can't I can't do a
retake on this one because I can't keep
talking so I have a maximum of two to
five minutes to say what is in my heart
which literally is nothing at the moment
just fine there's not gonna be days
there's gonna be days where there is
nothing to say I wanted to do a video on
the political app that I would love to
create but I'm not gonna do that justice
today with my throat the way it is and I
want to write down some points to talk
about that I'm chapter four of the
completion process and I'm enjoying
reading that book but anytime I read a
book I mean that might be why my throat
hurts because I've been nappy and while
reading it it is a lot it is a lot for
my brain to process when I read so I
have a weird unique place in this
universe I have a lot of limitations and
at the same time I've been given the
gift the understanding of how we create
a better world for everyone so
navigating my own personal life of
limitations well to the best of my
ability putting out taking the next
steps to make the global cooperative and
realizing very strongly this week that I
don't have the same lessons appear again
and again and again but I'm doing what
I'm supposed to be doing
although I would love to be able to make
better videos I would love to be able to
actually run a Facebook group so could
get somewhere all I'm supposed to
was communicated the idea and even that
I don't feel I'm up to par with with not
the greatest dad and I watch other
people's videos and they're much more
eloquent I can explain their ideas but I
also know when I can explain the idea
and it's when people ask questions so
eventually there won't be people
watching this asking questions not this
one
please don't watch this one I just
keeping up with my limits of posting
daily saying what is they're having some
be good and some be bad that is happy
create a better world is keep trying
keep failing in the right direction
first me as an individual and then
whatever group comes into being through
me doing what I can able to do and
eventually we have the social media
platform and the technology that is
created through the conversations that
we have on the social media platform to
create the social media platform
designed for a meaningful conversation
where people come for meaningful
conversation and to create the tools
needed to problem-solve the out of
all of the issues we are facing at the
moment and as we create more and more
tools to be able to tackle to be able to
understand the issues and connect and
live better lives ourselves the more
we're going to unleash our capacity to
do what we're here to do as individuals
which is create and invent and discover
and connecting with other human beings
right now most people on this planet me
included even though I've done a hell of
a lot of work not to be are scared and
lonely and disconnected and when we
solve a fraction of that the world gets
better immensely that is where a lot of
the addiction is coming from it's where
a lot of the violence is coming from and
we give when we start listening to
people and give people the ability to
really connect with each other and hear
each other out and the tools to problem
solve their own problems with
leaving it up to corporations or
governments and also not having to do it
all on your own you can actually matched
up with people share your same issues
and can problem solve solutions we
massively overhauled this planet
overnight because for every problem
there are people who are passionate and
committed to solving that problem and if
we allow them to they will solve it for
all of our benefit and that is my five
minutes and my throat is hurting so I am
going to go and I will see you tomorrow